Mishell Eugenia Angulo Villacis

Guayaquil, Ecuador

mishell angulo@hotmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/mishell-angulo-villacis/

+593988374298

Summary

Passionate computer science engineer with over 3 years of experience in designing and developing software applications, with a strong focus on JavaScript oriented technologies. Focused on problem solving based on collaborative work. Committed to delivering high-quality, efficient, and adaptable solutions, always eager to learn and work with new technologies.

Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Python
- SQL / NoSQL
- Java
- Postman

- PHP
- ReactJS
- React Native
- NodeJS
- Git
- Windows/Linux
- Agile

- Adaptability
- Communication
- Teamwork
- Problem solving

Experience

<u>JelouAl</u>

Guayaquil, Ecuador

Frontend developer

July 2023 - November 2023

- Developed solutions for web applications with frontend ReactJS.
- Developed solutions and support for mobile application with React Native.
- API Testing with Postman.

Devsusoftware

Guayaquil, Ecuador

Software developer

September 2021 - June 2023

- Managed effective solutions to incidents and bugs reported through tickets by the support financial areas with fintech tool Beclever.
- Developed solutions for web applications with frontend ReactJS.
- Developed technical documentation, reports, and testing schedulers.
- Data filtering with Python.
- API Testing with Postman.

PacificSoft S.A.

Guayaquil, Ecuador

Intern / Junior software developer

March 2019 - March 2021

- Developed C#, HTML applications and microservices for IoT focused projects.
- Development of IoT platform based on ThingsBoard.
- IoT product testing.
- Developed technical documentation, reports, and testing schedulers.

Education

- Computer Science Engineer
 Escuela Superior Politécnica del Litoral Guayaquil, Ecuador
- Frontend Program
 Universidad Hemisferios / Épico GYE Guayaquil, Ecuador

Certifications

- Microsoft Office Specialist
- EF SET Certification Level C1.